<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ProjectLuna</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_text">Project Luna</string>
    <string name="new_story_text">New Story</string>
    <string name="continue_story_text">Continue Story</string>
    <string name="end_story_text">End Story</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scene_view">SceneView</string>
    <string name="about_title">About</string>
    <string name="about_message">Project Luna created by Tyler Carney</string>
    <string name="reset_title">Reset Story</string>
    <string name="scene1_01_text">Welcome to Outpost Luna. Current records show you have a month left
                                on tour til your return to Earth. \nAutonomous Mining Rover Alpha 01 (AMR Alpha 1)
                                reported a problem. Assist the rover.</string>
    <string name="option1_scene1_01_text">Walk to Autonomous Mining Rover Alpha 01</string>
    <string name="option2_scene1_01_text">Drive manned rover to AMR Alpha 01</string>
    <string name="scene2_01_text">You go to get your spacesuit and notice a slight tear on the left arm fabric.
                                    You won\'t survive on out on the surface with the tear. There is some
                                    ducktape nearby that could be used to patch the tear temporarily. Else
                                    you will have to wait til a new arm piece can be fabricated. Which will
                                    take a day. The company really needs the AMR Alpha 01
                                    operational as soon as possible though</string>
    <string name="option1_scene2_01">Temporarily patch the tear with ducktape</string>
    <string name="option2_scene2_01">Wait for a new arm piece to be fabricated</string>
    <string name="scene3_01_text">The ducktape patch held up. You were able to reach the AMR Alpha 1.
                                        It was just stuck on a medium sized moon rock. Well now you have a real
                                        moon rock to take home with you to Earth.</string>
    <string name="scene3_02_text">By deciding to wait you chose safety before risk. The company understand
                                    but when they are on a deadline they feel to much time has been wasted.</string>
    <string name="scene2_02_text">A need for speed, huh. Think of the view you could have gotten by walking
                                    though. Your almost to AMR Alpha 1 and notice that there are small mounds
                                    in the path to the rover. With the low gravity on the moon going over the mounds at
                                    a high speed will mostly likely propel the rover upwards and off the surface for
                                    a few meters.</string>
    <string name="option1_scene2_02">Go for style points! Full speed over the mounds</string>
    <string name="option2_scene2_02">Take it slow over the mounds</string>
    <string name="scene3_03_text">Well your certainly would get the points if you were in an offroad race.
                                    Unfortunately for you landed on top of AMR Alpha 1. Destorying it beyond repair.
                                    The bosses won\'t be too happy with this news. Well it is time for you
                                    to think about changing your profession. Maybe give the new lunar offroad
                                    racing a try. I hear they are looking for experienced drivers.</string>
    <string name="scene3_04_text">They always said the turtle will always win the race. It\'s true again. Though
                                    probably less fun. You made it to AMR Alpha 1. Finding that is was just
                                    hindered by a medium sized moon rock and you can keep the moon rock
                                    as a reward.</string>
</resources>
